<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: reading | Steve Gricci]]></title>
  <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/blog/categories/reading/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-27T10:05:45-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://sgricci.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Steve Gricci]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://ryandeussing.com/">Ryan Deussing</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent reads]]></title>
    <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/2013/01/26/recent-reads/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-26T21:51:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sgricci.github.com/2013/01/26/recent-reads</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I've been reading more than ever recently. I decided I'd share a few of my
favorite books from recent reading over the holidays. Mostly sci-fi and
dystopia ahead, be warned.</p>

<h2>Ready Player One</h2>

<p>This book is one of the rare ones.  It really struck a chord with me, and I
couldn't put it down.  I consumed it over the course of a work day.</p>

<p>The book revolves around an immersive MMORPG called Oasis.  The eccentric creator
of this gaming world hides a series of puzzles in the game,
which is revealed after he has died. The story follows the hunt for this
set of puzzles and an all out war to be the first to reach the last puzzle.</p>

<p>As with most good books, there is also a love interest, and DeLoreans that achieve
light speed.</p>

<p><em>Rating: 5/5</em></p>

<h2>Ender's Game</h2>

<p>This book.. was amazing.  It's actually part of a quintet, but I feel the first
book ends in such a way, it is optional whether you read the other 3. (I haven't)</p>

<p>This book is futuristic, with population-density issues, and a
"big brother"/overwatcher feel to it.  The ending is amazing, and it's another book
that I really couldn't put down and recommended to a few friends immediately after
finishing the last page.</p>

<p>This book revolves around Ender, who at the beginning of the book is a young gifted
boy, a third child.  Third being a rather big deal, as special permission from the
government is required, due to population control laws. Ender and his two siblings
are geniuses. There is also a seemingly never-ending war against what is reffered
to as the "bugs", an alien race that desires to exterminate the human race. This book
takes place a decade of so after the second war with the bugs.</p>

<p><em>Rating: 5/5</em></p>

<h2>Wool #1-5</h2>

<p>Wool has been talked about quite a bit. It's a self-published phenomenon.</p>

<p>The series is actually 5 short stories.  They all tend to revolve around different
aspects of a place called "The Silo".  The Silo is an underground living quarters
that has been the home of the current inhabitants, or their ancestors for as long
as anyone can remember.</p>

<p>At the time I read the book, the first story (an easy 50 or so pages) was free on
amazon. Remember, the first hit is always free.</p>

<p>A few of the stories seem to draw it out quite a bit. In the second book, the
mayor and deputy go from the top of the silo, down around 130 flights to award
someone the honor and office of being the silo sheriff.  That book specifically
seemed to be overly descriptive. Oh, they go back up as well.</p>

<p>Overall, I liked the story in full, even if it seemed a bit scatter-brained
at times.</p>

<p>There are 2 other books (6,7), but they are prequels to the Wool saga, and the
fifth book leaves it at a good place.  I'm not specifically interested in how it
all began, as it's generically described in the books.</p>

<ul>
<li>Rating: 3/5*</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
