<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: keyboard | Steve Gricci]]></title>
  <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/blog/categories/keyboard/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-27T09:36:48-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://sgricci.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Steve Gricci]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://ryandeussing.com/">Ryan Deussing</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My experience with dasKeyboard]]></title>
    <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/2013/03/24/my-experience-with-daskeyboard/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-24T13:34:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://sgricci.github.com/2013/03/24/my-experience-with-daskeyboard</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My keyboard is quite important to me. I spend a lot of time using it.  I even
use Vim with arrow keys disabled (using hjkl instead).</p>

<p>I bought a <a href="http://www.daskeyboard.com">dasKeyboard</a> at the end of February and
have had nothing but issues with it ever since I received it. The following is a
timeline of my experience so far with dasKeyboard, to be used as a warning
for anyone considering purchasing one of these keyboards.</p>

<p>On February 26th, 2013, I purchased a <a href="http://www.daskeyboard.com">dasKeyboard</a> from
Amazon. (I purchased through Amazon rather than dasKeyboard because I have Prime)</p>

<p>The keyboard arrived the following Thursday (February 28th, 2013).</p>

<p>On March 7th 2013, the following keys stopped working completely: 8ik,.  I immediately
went to Amazon and reported the issue, and requested that a replacement be sent out.
Amazon sent one out immediately and gave me all necessary paperwork to send the old
one back to them free of charge. Shit happens.</p>

<p>On March 11th, 2013, the replacement dasKeyboard arrived. And there was much
rejoicing.</p>

<p>On March 22nd, 2013, the replacement dasKeyboard dies. No keys work at all. Tested
on two machines.  All the indicator lights stay on steady while
it's plugged in.  No keys work at all.</p>

<p>I've put in a support ticket to dasKeyboard, as I'm sure this could be just
a coincidence.</p>

<p>As of writing this, I haven't heard back from them either on twitter or via email
support.  I'll likely just return the keyboard to Amazon for a refund.</p>

<p>In other news, turns out there is a <a href="http://www.microcenter.com">Micro Center</a> in
the Denver Tech Center.  I just went and picked up a CM Storm QuickFire keyboard with
Cherry MX Blues. Here's to hoping I have better luck with this keyboard.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
