<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: timer | Steve Gricci]]></title>
  <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/blog/categories/timer/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-24T13:59:20-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://sgricci.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Steve Gricci]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[WFH Pro Tip: Set a timer]]></title>
    <link href="http://sgricci.github.com/blog/2013/01/19/wfh-pro-tip-set-a-timer/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-19T09:44:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://sgricci.github.com/blog/2013/01/19/wfh-pro-tip-set-a-timer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Having a bit of a problem getting yourself to step away from the desk?</p>

<p>When I first started working from home full-time, I had this problem as well.  I was overly communicative via email, IM, etc.  It turns out most people will notice this, but people don't notice if you reply in a normal amount of time. It's <strong>expected</strong> behavior.</p>

<p>For lunch, I realized it takes me a whole 8 minutes to make a sandwich, glass of water and consume it.  Your results are probably similar.  I started using a timer to specify how long I was going to stay away from my computer. When it was lunch time, I'd set my timer for an hour. During this time, I would not touch my computer, or check e-mail on my phone.  It was tough for the first few weeks, training my brain this way.</p>

<p>After I got over the hump, it was magical.  I usually don't use the timer any more, but I still stay away from my desk for at least an hour during the day. I eat lunch, I read on my kindle, I hang outside with my dogs and catch up on twitter, facebook, etc.</p>

<p>By the way, the non-Kindle Fire Kindles don't have e-mail. That's a feature. Disconnect <strong>more</strong>, it's good for you.</p>

<p>-s</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
